impulsetoday.com 2017-11-13

# Privacy Policy - Impulse Today

Impulse Today takes the matter of privacy very seriously. Please take the time to read through the policy below. If you have any further questions about the terms of this policy and how your information is handled please email [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#67040809130604130e0a17120b1402130803061e27000a060e0b4904080a).

The use of the Web Site(s) and/or software and any services and products (collectively, the “Web Site”) are subject to the provisions of this Privacy Policy, including any amendments or updates hereto. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Web Site.

## General

We take your privacy seriously. We gather certain types of information about our users and we want to help you understand the terms related to the collection and use of the information we collect. This Privacy Policy discloses the types of information we gather, how we use it, and what choices you have regarding the collection of such information. BY USING, ACCESSING OR DOWNLOADING THE WEB SITE), YOU AGREE TO THE COLLECTION AND USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION (AS HEREUNDER DESCRIBED), ALL IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET HEREUNDER. We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time and without notice, and it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy for any changes. Your use of the Web Site following any amendment of this Privacy Policy will signify your assent to and acceptance of its revised terms. If you are under the age of 13, and you are not eligible to use the Web Site, we ask you not to submit any personal information to us. Please note that any video, image, or other content posted at the direction of users onto the Web Site becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy.

## Collection of Information Personal Information.

Use of certain features of the Web Site may require submission of certain personal information, including your first and last name, email address, a nickname (or other user ID) and a password.

## Non personally identifiable Information

We may also collect or receive additional non-personally identifiable usage information specifically related to the use of a particular feature or offering on the Web Site, and responses to the offerings and advertisements presented on the Web Site.

We may also collect or receive (in some cases as part of the internet communication protocol) certain non-personally identifiable technical information, when the Web Site and pages are visited or when a client is used.

## How is the information being used?

The information is used to operate and improve the features, offerings and content presented to you, to personalize the content and advertisements provided to you; to fulfill your requests for products, programs, and services; to communicate with you and respond to your inquiries; to conduct research about your use of the Web Site; and to help offer you other products, programs, or services that may be of interest. Please note that we may use your personally identifiable information to present offers to you on behalf of business partners and advertisers. However, while our business partners and advertisers may receive aggregate data about our users, any personally identifiable information of yours will not be shared with third parties unless you have consented to the sharing of this information. Notwithstanding the foregoing, your information may be accessed and disclosed if and as required by legal procedures, as determined by us in good faith. Furthermore, we may transfer personally identifiable information in the event of a transfer of ownership or any of its Web Sites or products, in which case the information could become subject to a different privacy policy.

## Cookies

We may use cookies, web beacons or similar technologies to enhance and personalize your experience of the Web Site, including to operate and improve offerings through the Web Site; to help authenticate your identity when you visit and transact with the Web Site; to remember your preferences and registration information; to present and help measure and research the effectiveness of the various offerings, advertisements, and e-mail communications (by determining which e-mails you open and act upon); and to customize the content and advertisements provided to you. We does not require that you accept cookies, and you may disable cookies at any time. However, some functionality of our Web Site may be impaired if you decline to accept cookies. To disable cookies, follow the instructions in your web browser.

## Local Shared Object (Flash Cookie)

We may use local shared objects, sometimes known as Flash cookies, to store your preferences or display content based upon what you view on our site to personalize your visit. Our advertisers and third-party service providers also may use Flash cookies to collect and store information. Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how data is stored. Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies, please click here. If you disable Flash cookies, you won’t have access to many features that make your guest experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. Click here to cancel an existing account.

## Behavioral Targeting and Third Party Advertising

Our advertisers may use third party ad networks and ad serving companies to help sell and present advertisements online in connection with the Web Site. These third party ad companies may use cookies, web beacons or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, to help measure and research the advertisements’ effectiveness, compile anonymous statistics about Web Site users, to serve you advertisements tailored to interests you have shown by browsing on this and other sites you have visited, to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before and to avoid sending you duplicate advertisements. In so doing, these vendors may collect non-personal data such as your browser type, your operating system, Web pages visited, time of visits, content viewed, ads viewed, and other clickstream data. The use of these technologies by these third party ad companies is subject to their own privacy policies, not our policy, and we disclaims all liability in connection therewith. These third party ad companies may also monitor the Web Site for the purpose of reporting Web Site traffic, statistics, advertisements, “click-throughs” and/or other activities. We work with the following ad networks, whose privacy policies are available on their respective sites: Google, OpenX, AppNexus, and Rubicon. You may opt out of having the advertising that you see on our site targeted specifically to you by going to the respective sites’ privacy policy(ies) and following the directions. For example, to opt out of OpenX’s “interest-based ads” and to learn more about OpenX’s collection of your personal information to serve ads in connection with the Web Site, visit http://openx.com/legal. You can disable cookies, including those used by ad networks, by following the instructions in your web browser. We does not provide advertisers access to any personally identifiable information that you have provided to us (keeping in mind that anything you have elected to share publicly on the site is available to everyone to see).

**Last updated: October 15, 2014.**

## Security

We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect and safeguard the personally identifiable information under our control from unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification, unlawful destruction or accidental loss. All our personnel that have access to, and are associated with the processing of your personally identifiable information, are obligated to respect the confidentiality of the information.

## Special Note for Parents

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, we do not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information on the Web Site from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of our Web Site is directed to persons under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not provide any personally identifiable information on our Web Site. If we learn that personally identifiable information of persons under 13 years of age has been collected on the Web Site without verified parental consent, then we will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.
